<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alix Pham</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Alix Pham</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Recommendations</title>
      <link>/projects/recommendations/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/recommendations/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I have assembled a list of things I recommend. It goes from objects to own to podcasts and must-reads.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>EA Lausanne</title>
      <link>/projects/ea-lausanne/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/ea-lausanne/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I joined the Effective Altruism community early 2021. This post describes my journey and my commitments.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website building</title>
      <link>/posts/2023-02-08-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/2023-02-08-website/</guid>
      <description>Walk-through on how I made this website
Installation
install git install hugo Set up repo for Github Page
follow these instructions Create Hugo site and download theme
create new Hugo site by running hugo new site &amp;lt;&amp;lt;your repo name&amp;gt;&amp;gt; --force with the name of the Github Pages repo you downloaded download a theme, for example the poison theme if you know you won&amp;rsquo;t change the theme: use git clone &amp;lt;&amp;lt;theme-url&amp;gt;&amp;gt; /themes/&amp;lt;&amp;lt;theme name&amp;gt;&amp;gt; if you will make changes: fork the theme GitHub repo, then: git submodule add &amp;lt;&amp;lt;forked-theme-url&amp;gt;&amp;gt; themes/&amp;lt;&amp;lt;theme-name&amp;gt;&amp;gt; Add content and test locally</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/about/</guid>
      <description>Email me: alix.kl.pham@gmail.com
Originally from Toulouse, France, I currently live in Lausanne, Switzerland.
I am interested in1: alternative proteins: meat, eggs, and dairy products not made from living animals&amp;mdash;cheap, tasty, and healthy alternatives can decrease animal product consumption, thus farmed animal suffering and the negative environmental impact of agriculture resilient foods: foods, food production methods or interventions that would allow for significant food availability in the face of a global catastrophic food shock biosecurity and biosafety: managing risks from biological agents and their products policy: governments are very powerful, and control significant proportions of world GDP; helping policy-makers can be a high-value strategy Projects I undertook: EA Lausanne: Effective Altruism local chapter in Lausanne; community-building, speaker events, debates, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Existential Risk Research</title>
      <link>/projects/existential-risk-research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jan 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/existential-risk-research/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Resilient food sources are investigated by the Alliance to Feed the Earth in Disasters (ALLFED) in case of a catastrophe resulting in an abrupt reduction of sunlight&amp;mdash;nuclear war, supervolcanic eruption, asteroid impact. My role in this research cohort was to identify healthy diet combinations and mitigate possible deficiencies using those resilient food sources.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
